Contact

dmc419@comcast.net

www.linkedin.com/in/dianecostanzo3813612 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Healthcare Management Hospitals Clinical Research

Certifications

Diane M Costanzo
Diane M Costanzo
Diane M Costanzo

Diane Costanzo MSN,MSHA,RN,NE-BC,CMSRN

Nurse Supervisor-CHHA at Samaritan Healthcare & Hospice Mount Laurel, New Jersey

Summary

Highly accomplished healthcare leader with demonstrated experience in clinical operations and development. Skilled in Creating and Redesigning workflow processes, Performance Improvement, and Leadership.

Experienced Adjunct Faculty Member with a demonstrated history of working in the higher education industry. Skilled in Disease Management, Nursing Education, and Nursing Leadership.

Strong professional with a Master of Science-Nursing focused in Nursing Education from Thomas Edison State University and Master of Science Health Administration from St.Joseph's University.

Experience

Samaritan Healthcare & Hospice Nurse Supervisor-CHHA May 2019 - Present (1 year 3 months)

Virtua Health 14 years 2 months

AVP/Administrator Virtua Home Health January 2016 - December 2018 (3 years)

Patient Care Administrator-Director of Nursing-Homecare November 2004 - December 2015 (11 years 2 months)

Rowan University
Adjunct Faculty Member-Nursing
January 2010 - August 2013 (3 years 8 months)

Virtua Homecare

Director Of Quality Improvement October 2003 - November 2004 (1 year 2 months)

Virtua Health
18 years 10 months
Six Sigma Black Belt
January 2001 - October 2003 (2 years 10 months)

Nurse Manager- Medical/Surgical January 1985 - January 2001 (16 years 1 month)

Education

Thomas Edison State University

Master of Science-Nursing, Nursing Education · (2007 - 2010)

Saint Joseph's University -Philadelphia

Master of Science - MS in Health Administration, Health/Health Care

Administration/Management · (1990 - 1994)

Widener University
Bachelor of Science in Nursing - BSN, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse